Michael Jacquemart

Web developer - Product management

ADDRESS 60 rue des béguines, 4350 Momalle BELGIUM

PHONE +32 495 11 35 11

michaeljacquemart.webdev
@gmail.com

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN

michael-jacquemart-85bbb2143

GITHUB

michaeljacquemart

Junior Web Developer specializing in web product management. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Wellversed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3, MySQL, C, MATLAB and a bit of Python.

EDUCATION

2006 - 2012 O CESS

Athénée Royal de Waremme: MATH8/scientific.

2013 - 2018 © Engineering

University of Liège: Unfinished Bachelor in electricity and electronics.

2019 – may to december

Coding bootcamp

Becode.org: 7 months of web development.

EXPERIENCE

2013-14

Summers of O LAURENTY Rénovation

Building laborer: Floor tiling, prep work.

Summers of 2015-16 **o** Ethias

Accounting: Balances verification, differences justifications on Excelsheets (savings, insurance, etc.) and use of the Ethias Intranet. Excel study of customer histories: comparison of fees by region, type of customer, age, etc.

2019 O Becode.org

Junior web developer: Exercising in real situations and projects.